Guide to the Human Resources Office, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Human Resources Office, Yale University, records
1974-1988
RU 545
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
3
(5 boxes)
The records consist of minutes, correspondence, budgets, manuals, memoranda, and handbooks of the Yale Human Resouces Office. The records document personnel, committees, expenses, and labor unions.
Yale University. Dept of Human Resources
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 5-G (YRG 5-G), Records documenting personnel services at Yale University.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of minutes, correspondence, budgets, manuals, memoranda, and handbooks of the Yale Human Resouces Office. The records document personnel, committees, expenses, and labor unions.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
College personnel management; Personnel management; Universities and colleges -- Administration; Universities and colleges -- Employees -- Labor unions; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University. Dept of Human Resources
- Records, 1974-1983; Accession 1988-A-077
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2019.
  - Personnel Manual, 1977-1983 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Memos and Handbooks, 1974-1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Records, 1984-1988; Accession 1989-A-031
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2024.
  - Press Statements, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Contracts, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Information Binder, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Personnel
    - Strike, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Statistics, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Contract Strategies, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Clerical & Technical Exempt (Non-Striking), 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Negotiations/Salaries, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Arbitration, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Yale and Local 34, 1984 November 29 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Moratorium, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Mediation, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Partial Contract, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Strike Suspension, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Post Strike, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Student Lawsuit, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Local 34 Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - University Communications, 1985-1985 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Local 35, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Joint Job Description Committee Working File, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Joint Committe: Members & Chair, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Joint Job Description Committee Minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Job Description Public Hearing Notes, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Joint Committee Report, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Department of Human Resources Job Description Report Submitted to Joint Committee, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Managerial & Professional Benefits Committee, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 26 - 28)
  - Managerial & Professional, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 29 - 30)
  - Managerial & Professional Increases, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 31 - 32)
  - Department of Human Resources Budget: 1986-1987, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 33 - 34)
  - Personnel: Budget: Fiscal Year 1985-1986, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Personnel record of Kevin Lynn, 1975; Accession 1990-A-146
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2051.
  - Personnel record of Kevin Lynn, 1975 (Box 1)
- Staff Position Control Committee minutes, 1982-1983; Accession 2009-A-215
  - Staff Position Control Committee minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 1)